purge all assets from fotd✓
make a story.lua for setting basic things like spawn map
no art, use a blue box as a base, this will be collision 45x45 (px)✓
grid based this time, go for broke✓
map maker (allocated to dean)
ifonscreen function, if object >0 and < screenwidth✓
accel for jumping✓


[story]
stupid rpg typical shit, giant purple portal opens up and semi realistic pixel hand comes through and grabs the player